anti-business billionaire. These people
are so obsessed about one thing, and
that's the quality of the product
they're making. They make non-financial
decisions. Like Steve Jobs making sure
that the inside of the Mac looks
beautiful even though you can't open it
up and it costs more money. He doesn't
care. He wants the best product. James
Dyson's like this. He's an anti-business
billionaire. Yvon Chouinard, founder of
Patagonia, anti-business billionaire.
These guys, they're obsessed with two
things, quality of the product they're
making and retaining control of their
company over the long term. And the
funny part about that, the reason I call
them anti-business billionaires is
because if you make the world's best
product and you retain control over your
company, you wind up with the money
anyways.